A Guide to the Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1984-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1984-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.891
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1989 July 18.
Contents List
- SERIES I: Topical Files
  - Administration-General File 1983-1986 (Box 1)
  - Administration-Breakfast with O'Neil 1986 Apr 8 (Box 1)
  - Administration-Performance Objectives (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-General (2 folders) 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-Maintenance Backlog 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-On Line Catalogue 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing Services-Audit Report 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Albemarle County-General 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association-General 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - American Heart Association-General 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Architectural and Engineering Service-General 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Asbestos Litigation 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Assistant Vice President for Finance-Comptroller's Office 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Assistant Vice President for Finance-Overhead Cost 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Assistant Vice President for Personnel 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Assistant Vice President for Physical Plant 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Associate Provost for Research 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Associated General Contractors 1986 Jan 10 (Box 2)
  - Association of University Architects Conference 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Athletic Department-U.Va. 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Attorney General Law Conference 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Telephone System Audit-General 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Auditors Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Auxiliary Service-General 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors (2 folders) 1986 Mar, May 30 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors Meeting (2 folders) 1986 Jan 30-31, Oct 10-11 (Box 3)
  - Budget Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  - Budget Office-Addendum Proposal 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  - Budget Office-Biennial Budget (2 folders) 1984-1988 (Box 3)
  - Budget Office-Planning Assumptions 1986 (Box 4)
  - Budget Office-Proposed Budgets 1986 (Box 4)
  - Budget Office-Secretary Finley Visit 1985 Oct 18 (Box 4)
  - Capital Budget Programs-General 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Capital Budget Programs-Capital Outlay Report 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Capital Outlay-Briefing Sessions 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Capital Outlay Tour 1985 Jul 17 (Box 4)
  - Center for Innovative Technology 1986 (Box 4)
  - Center for Study of Higher Education-General 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Chamber of Commerce-General 1986 (Box 4)
  - Chamber of Commerce Task Force-Organization 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Charlottesville, City of-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Presentation to the Leadership- Charlottesville1985 (Box 5)
  - City of Charlottesville-Vinegar Hill Project 1985 (Box 5)
  - Charlottesville/Albemarle Metropolitan Planning Organization-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - City/County Planning Commission meetings 1986 Feb 2 (Box 5)
  - Citizens Committee for City, County Cooperation (The 5 C's)-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Clinch Valley College 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate School of Business Administration-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Commencement Exercises 1986 (Box 5)
  - Commerce School-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Commerce School-Annual Report 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Commerce School-Central Virginia Chapter American Marketing Association 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Commerce School-Faculty Meeting 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Commerce School-Marketing Group 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Communication Services-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education Division-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Dean of Students-General 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Decentralization Meetings (1 of 2) 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Decentralization Meetings (2 of 2) 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Decentralization Meetings-Secretary Fogarty 1983-1985 (Box 6)
  - Decentralization-List of the 7 Items 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Development Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Development Office-Post Campaign Funds 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Education, School of-General 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Emergency Operation-General 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Employee Communication Council-General 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Engineering and Applied Science School-General 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Environmental Health and Safety Office-General (2 folders) 1984-1986 (Box 6)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs-General 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs-Complaints 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs-Faculty Recruitment and Retention Plan 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs-OCR Visit 1986 Feb 25-26 (Box 7)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs-VA Plan employment 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science-Senate Meetings 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Food Service Division-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - General Electric Corporation Health Care Concerns-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - General Services-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - General Services-Communications 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - General Services-Material Management 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - General Services-New Hospital Telephones 1985 (Box 7)
  - General Services-Printing 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - General Services-Real Estate and Risk Management 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - General Services-Travel Service Contract 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Governmental and Legislature Relations-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Governmental and Legislature Relations-House and Senate Bills 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Governmental and Legislature Relations-Senate Bill # 122 1986 (Box 7)
  - Grievance Cases-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Housing Division-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Joint Dispatch Center 911 System-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Lawn Improvement Program-Lawn Advisory Board 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Legal Advisor's Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Material Management-General 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Medical Center-General 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Medical Center-Key Care Program 1986 (Box 8)
  - Medical Center Maintenance Study 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Montebello Circle (Bernice Hodock-water meter) 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Neighborhood Association-General 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Parking and Transportation Services-General 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Partners of the Americas-General 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Pavilions Renovation 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel Office-Annual Service Awards 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel Office-Apprenticeship Programs 1985 (Box 8)
  - Personnel Office-Audit 1985 (Box 8)
  - Personnel-Early Retirement Incentives-General 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel-Pay for Performance 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel-Retirement 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel-State Grievance Procedure 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel-Time-Income Trade Off 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel-T and R Administrator Positions 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Personnel-Training and Development 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Personnel-Workman's Compensation 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Personnel Administration-Thomas Kidd 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Physical Plant-General (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Physical Plant-Audit Report 1985 (Box 9)
  - Physical Plant-Tree Inventory 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Police Department-General 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Policy File-General 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - President's Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - President's Office-Council of Presidents 1985 (Box 9)
  - President's Office-Commonwealth Day 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Condition of Public Facilities 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Founder's Day 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Informal Retreat 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Interior Decorator 1985 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Moving Material and Moving Date 1985 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Position Descriptions 1985 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Refurbish Carr's Hill 1985 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Staff Meeting 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - President's Office-Transition Material 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Printing and Mail Service-General 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Provost Office-General 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Public Services 1985 (Box 10)
  - Purchasing and Accounts Payable Sys.--General 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-General (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-Clark Property and AAA Property 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-Fontaine Avenue 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-Liability Insurance 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-Proposed Insurance Legislation 1985- (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-Shoney's Property 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-Water Treatment Plant Lease 1985 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management-Wendell Wood Property 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Self-Study Program-General (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Self-Study-Physical Resources Committee 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - State Department of General Services-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - State Department of Information Technology-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - State Planning and Budget-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - State Publications-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Student Health Building Renovation-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Students-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Team International-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - TIAA Coverage-Retirement 1986 (Box 11)
  - TIAA Life Insurance 1986 (Box 11)
  - TIAA Plan 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Transportation System-General 1982-1986 (Box 11)
  - United Way-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Urban Land Institute-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Urban Land Institute-Real Estate Foundation 1985 (Box 11)
  - Urban Land Institute Plan Implementation-General 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Special Committee on Urban Land Institute-Board of Visitors 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Urban Land Institute-folders and booklets 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Urban Land Institute-Implementation Plan-City and County Relations 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Vice President and Provost-General 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance-General 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance-Virginia State University 1985 (Box 12)
  - Vice President for Health Affairs-General 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs-General 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - WVPT Board of Directors 1985-1986 (Box 12)
- SERIES II: Committee Files
  - Administrative Committees-General 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Advisory Committees-General 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Arboretum and Landscape Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Building Committees-Alderman Library 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Building Committees-Children's Rehab Center, Phase II 1986 (Box 12)
  - Building Committees-Chancellor's Home Clinch Valley College 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Building Committees-Darden School Research Center 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Building Committees-Heating Plant Expansion 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Building Committees-JAG Addition 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Building Committees-Medical Records Storage, McKim Hall 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Building Committees-Monroe Hall Addition 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Building Committees-Thornton Hall Addition 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Child Care Task Force (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Child Care Task Force-Papers, Pamphlets, and Brochures (2 folders) 1985 (Box 13)
  - Cemetery Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Committee to Study Capital Outlay Procedures (House Joint Resolution #34) 1985 (Box 13)
  - (Box 13)
  - Chapel Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Energy Conservation Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - General Faculty Task Force 1986 (Box 13)
  - Hospital Planning Committee-Programming Task Force 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Inauguration Committee for President O'Neil 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Map Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee 1984 Jun-Dec (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee-General 1985 Jan- (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee-1985 Annual Report 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee-Master Plan Development Subcommittee 1986 (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee-Parking Study Subcommittee 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee-Report 1985 (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee-Site Selection Subcommittee 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Master Plan Committee-ULI Subcommittee 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Replacement Hospital Executive Committee (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Replacement Hospital-Briefing 1984 (Box 15)
  - Replacement Hospital Committee-Hospital Project, Street Closing 1984 (Box 15)
  - Replacement Hospital Building Committee Meetings-Minutes 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Replacement Hospital Project-New Executive Committee (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Security and General Safety Committee 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - General Safety Committee 1982-1984 (Box 16)
  - Senior Executive Institute Advisory Committee 1985-1986 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Assault Task Force 1985-1986 (Box 16)
  - Special Funds Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 16)
  - Systems Planning Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 16)
  - University Hall-Fire Marshall 1986 (Box 16)
  - University Industry Technology Committee-General 1985-1986 (Box 16)
  - Use of University Resources Task Force 1986 (Box 16)
  - Vice President Planning Group-General 1985-1986 (Box 16)
- SERIES III: Planning and Budgeting Files
  - Accomplishments and Shortcomings 1984 Jul 1 (Box 16)
  - Accomplishments and Shortcomings-Administrative Computing 1984 Jul 1 (Box 16)
  - Accomplishments and Shortcomings-Equal Opportunity Programs 1984 Jul 1 (Box 16)
  - Accomplishments and Shortcomings-General Services 1984 Jul 1 (Box 16)
  - Accomplishments and Shortcomings-Personnel Administration 1984 Jul 1 (Box 16)
  - Accomplishments and Shortcomings-Physical Plant 1984 Jul 1 (Box 16)
  - Accomplishments and Shortcomings-Police Department 1984 Jul 1 (Box 16)
  - Biennial Evaluation--Accomplishments and Shortcomings 1982-1985 (Box 16)
  - Biennial Report-Summary 1984 (Box 16)
  - Budget 1985-1987 (Box 16)
  - Budget--Addendum 1984-1987 (Box 16)
  - Budget-Computing 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Budget-EOP 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Budget-General Services 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Budget-Physical Plant 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Budget-Personnel 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Budget-Police 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Budget-Preparation for the 1986-1987 Operation Budget 1985-1987 (Box 17)
  - Budget-V.P.'s Office 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Objectives and Strategies
  - Objectives and Strategies-Equal Opportunity Programs 1984 Aug 1 (Box 18)
  - Objectives and Strategies-Personnel Administration 1984 Aug 1 (Box 18)
  - Objectives and Strategies-Physical Plant 1984 Aug 1 (Box 18)
  - Objectives and Strategies-Police Department 1984 Aug 1 (Box 18)
  - Objectives and Strategies-Profiles and Reports (2 folders) 1984 (Box 18)
  - Objectives and Strategies-Report and Plan 1982-1990 (Box 18)
  - Performance Variables-Administrative Computing 1984 Jun 1 (Box 18)
  - Performance Variables-Equal Opportunity Programs 1984 Jun 1 (Box 18)
  - Performance Variables-General Services 1984 Jun 1 (Box 18)
  - Performance Variables-Personnel Administration 1984 Jun 1 (Box 18)
  - Performance Variables-Physical Plant Performance Variables 1984 Jun 1 (Box 18)
  - (Box 18)
  - Performance Variables-Police Department 1984 Jun 1 (Box 18)
  - Philosophies 1984 (Box 18)
  - Planning and Budgeting 1983-1984 (Box 18)
  - Planning for Administrative Support Services 1984-1986 (Box 18)
  - Standards of Performance-Administrative Computing 1984 Jul 1 (Box 19)
  - Standards of Performance-Equal Opportunity Programs 1984 Jul 1 (Box 19)
  - Standards of Performance-General Services 1984 Jul 1 (Box 19)
  - Standards of Performance-Personnel Administration 1984 Jul 1 (Box 19)
  - Standards of Performance-Police Department 1984 Jul 1 (Box 19)
  - Statements of Philosophy-Administrative Computing 1984 Apr 1 (Box 19)
  - Statements of Philosophy-Equal Opportunity Programs 1984 Apr 1 (Box 19)
  - Statements of Philosophy-General Services 1984 Apr 1 (Box 19)
  - Statements of Philosophy-Personnel Administration 1984 Apr 1 (Box 19)
  - Statements of Philosophy-Physical Plant 1984 Apr 1 (Box 19)
  - Statements of Philosophy-Police Department 1984 Apr 1 (Box 19)
  - Statements of Philosophy-Service Departments 1984 (Box 19)
- SERIES IV: Restricted Files (Box 20)